[Music]
[Applause]
karate night out was too much fun for me
because at la maza gujarati celebs a cut
munch for a comedy kurta collage bagua
morocco in a comedy factory in oj whose
ratty night out her teeth that was a
brilliant once in lifetime experience
Ashima omo jeopardy i'mna botanic stage
super a college experience improved for
medicare 1oj my first time jeju / k & b
zu k putin e good after loco napoli
where mess to scare you and a feel for
you vivo could manufacture in
inalienable good unite out is one of the
comedy factories most entertaining shows
nowhere else do you get to see such a
unique experience where cinema meets
comedy and even the audience it's not
just a mix of you know regular viewers
but also people from the film fraternity
and we found that they absolutely love
and enjoy the madness that's happening
on stage share karate movement Inca
theorem put the stagecoach the gay once
more of it whenever I get to once more
once more but I enjoyed to be a part of
a coach a night it was a really good
experience improv is is a form that I
really liked it was an experience to
remember for a long time I had gone to
Gujarati night out along with yoga the
one most memorable moment was when we
started roasting Mullen and he
completely did not know I don't know if
he was playing along and being dumb but
it was awesome - you know when we
started taking on him and he he's a good
soul
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
thank you so much to friends from the
Gujarati industry for being part of the
Gujarati I doubt that you supported me
gamma radiation at unity - in a boat
it's very overwhelming the audience a
Bernardo producer doppio will be back
with a bigger bang on a frequency
definitely a who's ready night out
Nevada racial thank you so much guys
thank you
[Applause]
hey guys thank you so very much
who's ready night out in a point from a
sudra theory gem response up your chip
or anybody live moments shaken about the
live show stadium I applaud nothing I'd
let you come and watch our live shows
but the updates of our social media
pages Perth on memory - a like share and
do not forget to subscribe to the comedy
factory our Elizabeth a Gujarati night
out our videos see you next year a very
happy new year